ajronline.org 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy

At ARRS, we are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring the security of your personal information. Because your privacy is important to you and to ARRS, ARRS will operate its web sites and any related mobile application, product or service, collectively referred to hereafter as ARRS’ Services, by the following principles. By using the ARRS Services, you consent to this privacy policy. 

**Personal Information:**  
There are portions of the ARRS Services that will ask you for personally identifiable information. This information, including first and last name, address, e-mail address, facsimile number, telephone number, and payment information, together with any additional information you provide to ARRS, will not be processed or disclosed by ARRS except as permitted by this policy or as required or allowed by applicable law or legal process.

**Use of Personal Information:**  
ARRS uses your personal information to operate the ARRS Services; to contact you; to effect, enforce, investigate, collect on, and account for transactions related to the ARRS; to maintain your entry as a member or customer of ARRS; to adjust ARRS’ offerings of products and services; to license mailing labels of ARRS members to include first name; last name; address including street name, city, state/province, and zip/postal code; and to comply with applicable law. ARRS uses outside companies to ship orders, to engage in conference, meeting and course planning and registration and to process credit cards when billing users for products and services. ARRS will endeavor to protect the security of personal information.

**Disclosure of Personal Information:**  
The ARRS Services may store and disclose personal information as allowed or required by applicable law, including but not limited to making disclosures that are necessary or advisable to: (a) conform to legal or regulatory requirements or comply with legal process; and (b) protect the rights, safety or property of ARRS, the ARRS Services or others (including but not limited to other providers, suppliers and vendors), or the users of the ARRS Services or the public.

**Use of Cookies:**  
Cookies are files with small amount of data that some websites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them to gather information regarding the sources of site traffic, or to maintain session information. Like many sites, ARRS uses cookies to retain session information and to serve SSO (Single Sign On) to different vendor service sites, such as our online journal publisher for the American Journal of Roentgenology (AJR), and our learning management system. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of the ARRS web sites.

**Google Analytics:**  
ARRS also uses Google Analytics to help analyze the performance of our website. ARRS does not combine personally identifiable information we obtain through other methods with data from Google Analytics. You can prevent Google Analytics from using cookies by installing the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On. To understand how Google uses data when you use partner sites, visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.

**Information We Share:**  
ARRS may share information obtained from attendees of courses, conferences, or meetings with carefully selected organizations including other associations, educational institutions, government agencies, exhibitors, and corporate partners.

**Protection of Personal Information:**  
ARRS endeavors to protect the security of data collected on the ARRS Services. ARRS has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information ARRS collects online in accordance with industry standards. When ARRS contracts with third parties to perform any supporting ARRS Services, ARRS will endeavor to protect the security of personal information.

**Process to Review and Update Personal Information:**  
ARRS members and customers have the ability to review and update their contact information using the ARRS Services. Contact information may be reviewed and updated under “My Profile” on the ARRS websites. The “edit” button allows members to update their contact information including first name; last name; address including street name, city, state/province, zip/postal code, and e-mail address.

**Opt-Out Policy:**  
ARRS members and customers have the right to opt-out of mailing lists and other marketing communications licensed by ARRS at any time. If you prefer to be excluded from mailing lists or any other marketing communications licensed by ARRS, please email the ARRS Member Services Team at [membership@arrs.org](mailto://membership@arrs.org).

**Policy Updates:**  
ARRS has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. ARRS will notify consumers of material changes made to the Privacy Policy on the front page of the Web site for 30 days from the time of implementation.

**Accountability:**  
If at any time you believe that the ARRS Web site has not adhered to these principles, please notify the American Roentgen Ray Society, 44211 Slatestone Ct., Leesburg, VA 20176-5109. [webmaster@arrs.org](mailto://webmaster@arrs.org).
